Register of the International Socialists Issuances, 1967-1976
Hoover Institution Archives
International Socialists Issuances
1967-1976
1972-1975
80162
Hoover Institution Archives
6 manuscript boxes (2.4 linear feet)
Internal bulletins, minutes, resolutions, reports, and discussion material relating to socialist political activity in the United States.
International Socialists
Box 1-5
Access
Collection open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Scope and Content
This collections contains materials related to the International Socialists group which was active during the late 1960s and 1970s in the United States. A bulk of the material is comprised of issues of I.S. Bulletin and caucus materials. Original folder names have been retained when possible.
Socialism--United States.; United States--Politics and government.
- Forum: An I.S. Discussion Bulletin, 1967-1970 (Text 1: 1-5)
- I.S. Bulletin, 1969-1971 (Text 1: 6-20)
- I.S. Bulletin, 1972-1973 (Text 2: 1-26)
- I.S. National Reports, 1972-1975 (Text 3: 1-3)
- International bulletins, 1972-1976 (Text 3: 4)
- Black caucus material, 1971-1976 (Text 3: 5)
- Gay caucus bulletin, October 1970 (Text 3: 6)
- Reorient Papers, 1970-1971 (Text 3: 7)
- International news, 1972-1973 (Text 3: 8)
- Women's caucus bulletins, 1970-1976 (Text 3: 9-11)
- Women's liberation material, 1972-1973 (Text 4: 1)
- Labor material, 1969-1976 (Text 4: 2-6)
- Tasks and Perspectives, 1970-1973 (Text 4: 7)
- I.S. Reports, 1969 (Text 4: 8-9)
- I.S. News of the Month, 1976 (Text 5: 1)
- Convention material, 1970-1976 (Text 5: 2-3)
- National Action Committee minutes, 1969-1973 (Text 5: 4)
- Economic material, 1971-1976 (Text 5: 5)
- High school caucus material, undated (Text 5: 6)
- Revolutionary Tendency material, undated (Text 5: 7)
- Left Faction, 1976 (Text 5: 8)
- Leninist Tendency, 1972-1973 (Text 5: 9)
- Bay area branches, 1970-1976 (Text 5: 10)
- Branch (various), 1969-1973 (Text 5: 11)
- "Documents of the Founding Convention,", September 1969 (Text 6: 1)
- Task and Perspective reports, 1970-1976 (Text 6: 2-7)
- I.S. Internal Miscellaneous, 1969-1976 (Text 6: 8)